<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Tagged Wallpaper</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_open">Open navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="navigation_drawer_close">Close navigation drawer</string>
    <string name="action_settings">Settings</string>
    <string name="pop_tags">Trending Tags On Flickr.com! more options coming soon</string>
    <string name="sel_image">Select an image</string>
    <string name="button_clicked">"Please wait"</string>
    <string name="clarifai_Info">"Clarifai is a image recognition system founded by Matthew Zeiler. Once an image has been selected, it will be sent to the Clarifai API for image recognition. Tags will be returned based off the image; however, image recognition is a very complex technology, this app cannot guarantee the accuracy of the returned tags. Enjoy."</string>
    <string name="title_activity_results">ResultsActivity</string>
    <string name="title_activity_photo">PhotoActivity</string>

    <string-array name="tag_sources">
        <item>Recommended</item>
        <item>Trending on Flickr</item>
    </string-array>


    <string name="disclaimer">Images are pulled off Flickr.com. This app is made to pull images off specific “safe” photo groups instead of the general pool of public photos. This way it can help prevent / minimize mature-rated photos. This also means that photo searches are based off a photo group instead of all the possible photos; this means there is limited amounts of tags that can be searched.\n\nEverything here is based on tags, so when searching for images be sure to “think like a tag” and be aware of spaces. E.g. searching “star wars” is not recommended over searching “starwars” due to the nature of the tagging system on Flickr.com.\n\nOne section of this app uses Clarifai which uses image recognition to identify tags based off photos you can select. These tags may or may not be correct due to the capabilities of the Clarifai service. Since any tags can occur after the image recognition is complete, there is no guarantee there will be any search results due to our attempt to block mature-rated photos.
    </string>

    <string name="clarifai_error">Error tagging this image</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="hello_blank_fragment">Hello blank fragment</string>


</resources>